Guide to the Oppenheimer collection of theater programs, 1906-1999 MS 489
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Houston theater season programs, 1960-1999; 60287
  - "The Will Rogers Follies," Miller Outdoor Theatre, 1995-07-12-1995-07-22; 60347 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Miss Saigon," Jones Hall, 1995-07-1995-09; 60346 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "42nd Street," Music Hall, 1995-09-21-1995-10-08; 60345 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "The Importance of Being Earnest," Alley Theatre, 1995-10-21-1995-11-18; 60344 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Wait Until Dark," Rice University, 1995-11-08-1995-11-11; 1995-11-15-1995-11-18; 60343 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Singin' in the Rain," Music Hall, 1995-11-30-1995-12-17; 60342 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Julius Caesar" in repertory with "Antony and Cleopatra," Alley Theatre, 1996-01-12-1996-02-11; 159787 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Carousel," Theatre Under the Stars, 1996-02; 159788 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "The Young Man From Atlanta," Alley Theatre, 1996-02-16-1996-03-16; 159789 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "A Streetcar Named Desire," Alley Theatre, 1996-03-29-1996-04-27; 159790 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "The Music Man," Theatre Under the Stars, 1996-03-07-1996-03-24; 159791 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "The Heiress," Alley Theatre, 1996-05-03-1996-06-01; 159792 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Me and My Girl," Theatre Under the Stars, 1996-05-16-1996-06-02; 159793 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "The Food Chain," Alley Theatre, 1996-05-17; 159794 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Inherit the Wind," Alley Theatre, October 16-November 16, 1996.; 159795 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "My Fair Lady," Theatre Under the Stars, October 10-13, 15-20, 22-27, 1996.; 1996-10-15-1996-10-20; 1996-10-22-1996-10-27; 159796 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Annie," Theatre Under the Stars, 1996-12; 159797 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Phantom," Music Hall, January 2-5, 7-12, 14-19, 1997.; 1997-01-02-1997-01-05; 1997-01-07-1997-01-12; 1997-01-14-1997-01-19; 60326 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Having Our Say," Alley Theatre, 1997-01-10-1997-02-08; 60325 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "The Greeks Part One—The War and the Murderers," Alley Theatre, 1997-02-28-1997-05-04; 60324 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Crazy For You," Music Hall, 1997-03-06-1997-03-23; 60323 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Picasso at the Lapin Agile," Alley Theatre, 1997-06; 60322 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "The Unexpected Guest," Alley Theatre, 1997-07-11-1997-07-27; 60321 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Death of a Salesman," Alley Theatre, 1997-10-03-1997-11-01; 60320 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Makin' Whoopee!," Music Hall, 1997-10-30-1997-11-16; 60319 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Oliver!," Music Hall, December 2-7, 9-14, 16-21, 1997.; 1997-12-09-1997-12-14; 1997-12-16-1997-12-21; 60318 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "The Black Theatre of Prague," (unknown theatre), (unknown date).; 60315 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "The Rink," (unknown theatre), 1998.; 60314 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Cakewalk," (unknown theatre), 1998.; 60313 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Four Dogs and a Bone," (unknown theatre), 1998.; 60312 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Angel Street: A Thriller," Alley Theatre, 1998-01-09-1998-02-07; 60311 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Gigi," Music Hall, 1998-01-14-1998-02-01; 60310 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Seven Guitars," Alley Theatre, 1998-02-13-1998-03-14; 60309 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Hot Shoe Shuffle," (unknown theatre), 1998-03; 60308 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Hydriotaphia," Alley Theatre, 1998-03-27-1998-04-25; 60307 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Noises Off," Alley Theatre, 1998-05-15-1998-06-14; 60306 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Victor/Victoria," Music Hall, 1998-05-10-1998-05-30; 60305 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Not About Nightingales," Alley Theatre, 1998-06-05-1998-07-03; 60304 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Zorro," (unknown theatre), 1998-08; 60303 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "The Civil War," Alley Theatre, 1998-09; 60302 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Scrooge," Arena Theatre, 1999-12-04-1999-12-19; 60300 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Funny Girl," Stages Repertory Theatre, 1999-01-03-1999-11-25; 60299 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "The Beauty of Queen Leenane," Alley Theatre, 1999-01-08-1999-02-06; 60298 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Hedda Gabler," Alley Theatre, 1999-02-19-1999-03-20; 60297 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Gross Indecency: The Three Trials of Oscar Wilde," Alley Theatre, 1999-04-02-1999-05-01; 60296 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Jesus Christ Superstar," Brown Theatre/Wortham Center, 1999-07-06-1999-07-11; 1999-07-13-1999-07-18; 60295 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Grand Hotel," Arena Theatre, 1999-10-12-1999-10-24; 60294 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "The Scarlet Pimpernel," (unknown theatre), 1999-08; 60293 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "The Importance of Being Earnest," Grace Theatre, July 9-August 15, 1999.; 60292 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "A View from the Bridge," Alley Theatre, September 24-October 23, 1999.; 60291 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Lemonade," Alley Theatre, October 8-November 7, 1999.; 60290 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Misalliance," Alley Theatre, May 14-June 13, 1999.; 60289 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Series III: London theater season programs, 1970-1994, 60243
  - "The Black Theatre of Prague," (unknown theatre), (unknown date).; 60285 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "California Suite," Eugene O'Neill Theatre, April 1977.; 60284 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Good Evening," Plymouth Theatre, March 1974.; 60283 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Same Time, Next Year," Brooks Atkinson Theatre, April 1977.; 60282 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Middle Age Spread," Lyric Theatre, May 1980.; 60281 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Evita," Prince Edward Theatre, May 1980.; 60280 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Death Trap," Garrick Theatre, May 1980.; 60279 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Summit Conference," Lyric Theatre, May 1982.; 60278 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Educating Rita," Piccadilly Theatre, May 1982.; 60277 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Barnum," London Palladium, May 1982.; 60276 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Amadeus," Her Majesty's Theatre, May 1982.; 60275 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Cats," New London Theatre, May 1982.; 60274 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "The Real Thing," Strand Theatre, May 1984.; 60273 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "The Business of Murder," Mayfair Theatre, May 1984.; 60272 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Benefactors," Vaudeville Theatre, May 1984.; 60271 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Pack of Lies," Lyric Theatre, May 1984.; 60270 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Noises Off," Savoy Theatre, May 1984.; 60269 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Noises Off," Brooks Atkinson Theatre, April 1984.; 60268 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Me and My Girl," Adelphi Theatre, October 1985.; 60267 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "42nd Street," Theatre Royal Drury Lane, October 1985.; 60266 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Little Shop of Horrors," Comedy Theatre, October 1983.; 60265 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Pravda: A Fleet Street Comedy," The Olivier Theatre, May 1985.; 60264 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Two Into One," Shaftesbury Theatre, October 1984.; 60263 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Brighton Beach Memoirs," The Variety theatre in Toronto, September 1986.; 60262 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Scrooge," Arena Theatre, December 4-19,1999.; 60260 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Run For Your Wife!," Whitehall Theatre, March 1989.; 60259 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Over My Dead Body," Savoy Theatre, March 1989.; 60258 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "The Phantom of the Opera," Her Majesty's Theatre, October 1986.; 60257 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Lettice and Lovage," The Globe, October 1987.; 60256 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "An Inspector Calls," Aldwych Theatre, September 1993.; 60255 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Present Laughter," Gate Theatre, June 1994.; 60254 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Les Misérables," The Palace Theatre, December 1985.; 60253 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Breaking the Code," Theatre Royal Haymarket, November 1986.; 60252 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "High Society," Victoria Palace Theatre, March 1987.; 60251 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Canaries Sometimes Sing," Albery Theatre, May 1987.; 60250 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "An Inspector Calls," Westminster Theatre, May 1987.; 60249 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Driving Miss Daisy," Apollo Theatre, June 1988.; 60248 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Company," Drama Theatre of the Sydney Opera House, January 1986.; 60247 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Follies," Shaftesbury Theatre, August 1987.; 60246 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Murder in the Cathedral," The Pit, 1994.; 60245 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Bound volumes of theater season programs, 1936-1968, 60129
  - Subseries A: Bound volume: Helen's Theatre, 1936-1939 theater season programs, 60147 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - "Dead End," Belasco Theatre, 1936-02; 60167
    - "Hamlet," The Imperial Theatre, November 1936.; 60166
    - "The Wingless Victory," The Empire Theatre, January 1937.; 60165
    - "The Women," Ethel Barrymore Theatre, February 1937.; 60164
    - "King Richard II," St. James Theatre, February 1937.; 60163
    - "The Masque of Kings," Sam S. Shubert Theatre, March 1937.; 60162
    - "Brother Rat," Biltmore Theatre, March 1937.; 60161
    - "Yes, My Darling Daughter," The Playhouse, September 1937.; 60160
    - "Susan and God," The Plymouth Theatre, October 1937.; 60159
    - "The Star-Wagon," The Empire Theatre, October 1937.; 60158
    - "Room Service," Cort Theatre, October 1937.; 60157
    - "Golden Boy," Belasco Theatre, November 1937.; 60156
    - "Many Mansions," Biltmore Theatre, November 1937.; 60155
    - "I'd Rather Be Right," Alvin Theatre, November 1937.; 60154
    - "Three Waltzes," Majestic Theatre, February 1938.; 60153
    - "Our Town," Morosco Theatre, April 1938.; 60152
    - "On Borrowed Time," Longacre Theatre, Auust 1938.; 60151
    - "Kiss the Boys Goodbye," Henry Miller's Theatre, November 1938.; 60150
    - "Knickerbocker Holiday," Ethel Barrymore Theatre, November 1938.; 60149
    - "No Time for Comedy," Ethel Barrymore Theatre, September 1939.; 60148
  - Subseries B: Bound volume: Helen's Theatre, 1947-1955 theater season programs, 60221 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Street Scene," Adelphi Theatre, March 1947.; 60219
    - "Tickets, Please!," Coronet Theatre, September 1950.; 60218
    - "Gentlemen Prefer Blondes," The Ziegfeld Theatre, September 1950.; 60217
    - "The Member of the Wedding," The Empire Theatre, September 1950.; 60216
    - "The Consul," Ethel Barrymore Theatre, September 1950.; 60215
    - "The Happy Time," The Plymouth Theatre, September 1950.; 60214
    - "Love and Let Love," Shubert Theatre, August 27-September 1, 1951.; 60213
    - "Affairs of State," The Music Box, September 1951.; 60212
    - "The Moon is Blue," Henry Miller's Theatre, September 1951.; 60211
    - "The King and I," St. James Theatre, September 1951.; 60210
    - "The Rose Tattoo," Martin Beck Theatre, September 1951.; 60209
    - "Guys and Dolls," Forty-Sixth Street Theatre, September 1951.; 60208
    - "Call Me Madam," The Imperial Theatre, September 1951.; 60207
    - "The Happy Time," Playhouse Theatre, March 1952.; 60206
    - "The Teahouse of the August Moon," Martin Beck Theatre, April 1955.; 60205
    - "Anastasia," Lyceum Theatre, May 1955.; 60204
    - "Tea and Sympathy," Forty-Eighth Street Theatre, May 1955.; 60203
    - "The Desperate Hours," Ethel Barrymore Theatre, May 1955.; 60202
    - "The Pajama Game," St. James Theatre, May 1955.; 60201
    - "Witness for the Prosecution," Henry Miller's Theatre, May 1955.; 60200
    - "The Pajama Game," St. James Theatre, May 1955.; 60199
    - "The Teahouse of the August Moon," Martin Beck Theatre, May 1955.; 60198
    - "Bus Stop," The Music Box, May 1955.; 60197
    - "The Seven Year Itch," Fulton Theatre, May 1955.; 60196
    - "The Boy Friend," Royale Theatre, May 1955.; 60195
    - "Silk Stockings," Imperial Theatre, May 1955.; 60194
    - "Plain and Fancy," Winter Garden, May 1955.; 60193
  - Subseries C: Bound volume: Helen's Theatre, 1957-1959 theater season programs, 60191 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - "Inherit the Wind," National Theatre, April 1957.; 60190
    - "My Fair Lady," Mark Hellinger Theatre, April 1957.; 60189
    - "Bells are Ringing," Sam S. Shubert Theatre, April 1957.; 60188
    - "Li'l Abner," St. James Theatre, April 1957.; 60187
    - "No Time for Sergeants," Alvin Theatre, April 1957.; 60186
    - "The Most Happy Fella," Imperial Theatre, April 1957.; 60185
    - "Separate Tables," The Music Box, April 1957.; 60184
    - "Auntie Mame,", April 1957.; 60183
    - "Middle of the Night," ANTA Theatre, May 1957.; 60182
    - "Happy Hunting," Majestic Theatre, May 1957.; 60181
    - "The Music Man," Majestic Theatre, December 1957.; 60180
    - "Flower Drum Song," Houston Music Theatre, November 1966.; 60179
    - "Flower Drum Song," St. James Theatre, December 1958.; 60178
    - "Gypsy," The Broadway Theatre, May 1959.; 60177
    - "J. B.," Anta Theatre, December 1958.; 60176
    - "A Raisin in the Sun," Ethel Barrymore Theatre, March 1959.; 60175
    - "A Touch of the Poet," Helen Hayes Theatre, October 1958.; 60174
    - "The World of Suzie Wong," The Broadhurst Theatre, October 1958.; 60173
    - "West Side Story," Winter Garden, October 1957.; 60172
    - "Redhead," Forty-Sixth Street Theatre, February 1959.; 60171
    - "A Majority of One," Sam S. Shubert Theatre, 1959.; 60170
    - "Rashomon," The Music Box, February 1959.; 60169
    - "The Threepenny Opera," Theatre de Lys, (unknown date).; 60168
  - Subseries D: Bound volume: Helen's Theatre, 1961-1965 theater season programs, 60242 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - "Hamlet," Phoenix Theatre, March 1961.; 60241
    - "Big Fish, Little Fish," Anta Theatre, March, 1961.; 60240
    - "The Unsinkable Molly Brown," Winter Garden, November 1960.; 60239
    - "Mary, Mary," Helen Hayes Theatre, March 1961.; 60238
    - "Bye Bye Birdie," Sam. S. Shubert Theatre, April 1960.; 60237
    - "Carnival!," Imperial Theatre, 1961.; 60236
    - "All the Way Home," Belasco Theatre, December 1960.; 60235
    - "Donnybrook!," Forty-Sixth Street Theatre, May 1961.; 60234
    - "The Sound of Music," Lunt-Fontanne Theatre, November 1959.; 60233
    - "Mark Twain Tonight!," 41st Street Theatre, (unknown date).; 60232
    - "How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying," Forty-Sixth Street Theatre, October 1961.; 60231
    - "Oliver!," Imperial Theatre, January 1963.; 60230
    - "Photo Finish," Brooks Atkinson Theatre, February 1963.; 60228
    - "Beyond the Fringe," John Golden Theatre, November 1962.; 60229
    - "Mr. President," St. James Theatre, November 1962.; 60227
    - "The Typists" and "The Tiger," Orpheum Theatre, (unknown date).; 60226
    - "Barefoot in the Park," Biltmore Theatre, November 1963.; 60225
    - "Funny Girl," Winter Garden, April 1964.; 60224
    - "Fiddler on the Roof," Imperial Theatre, October 1964.; 60223
    - "Luv," The Booth Theatre, November 1964.; 60222
  - Subseries E: Bound volume: Helen's Theatre, 1960-1968 theater season programs, 60130 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - "The Mousetrap," Ambassadors Theatre, 1961.; 60146
    - "The Irregular Verb to Love," Criterion Theatre, 1961.; 60145
    - "Folies Chéries," (unknown theatre), May 1961.; 60144
    - "Ross," Theatre Royal Haymarket, May 1960.; 60143
    - "Hostile Witness," Theatre Royal Haymarket, November 1964.; 60142
    - "The Plough and the Stars," The Queen's Theatre, September 1965.; 60141
    - "Robert and Elizabeth," Lyric Theatre, October 1964.; 60140
    - "The Edinburgh Military Tattoo," (unknown theater), 1965.; 60139
    - Various productions, Festival Fringe Society in Edinburgh, 1965.; 60138
    - "The Pedestrians," Y.M.C.A. Theatre, 1965.; 60137
    - "The Jew of Malta," Aldwych Theatre, 1964.; 60136
    - "Inadmissible Evidence," Wyndham's Theatre, March 1965.; 60135
    - "Charlie Girl," Adelphi Theatre, May 1968.; 60134
    - "Hadrian the Seventh," The Mermaid Theatre, May 1968.; 60133
    - "Fiddler on the Roof," Her Majesty's Theatre, May 1968.; 60132
    - "Man of La Mancha," Piccadilly Theatre, May 1968.; 60131